BONITA ROSA

543 Main Road, Baton Rouge, LA432I0 b.rosa@myemail.com (123)456-7890

Knowledgeable and skilled carpenter with 7+ years' experience erecting and repaining buildings and other wooden structures. Outstanding technical ability and capable of working to an exceptional degree of accuracy. Specialist knowledge of historical building preservation and authentic construction and repair techniques. Confident leader with a talent for coordinating large multi-disciplinary teams and mentorship.

EDUCATION

CERTIFICATE OF TECHNICAL STUDIES IN CARPENTRY

DELGADO COMMUNITY COLLEGE New' Orleans, LA. September 2009 - June 2013

KEY SKILLS

- Electric and pneumatic power tool operation
- Exce llent know Ledge of anchor bolt la_Vou,s
- Understanding of Symons Forms
- · Strong leadership skills
- Well-verged in construction site health and safety

CERTIFICATIONS

Certified Building Envelope
 Tcchnitian (CB ET), Carpenters
 International Certification Council,
 June 2018

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

CARPENTER

Cajun Industries, Baton Rouge, LA March 2015 - Present

- Work to precise technical specifications from blueprints and technical drawings
- Construct and install forms, batter boards, and scaffolds and ensure a flawless finish
- Coordinate and direct teams of laborers and other tradespeople on-site and supervise activities to ensure brief adherence and quality control
- Safely operate manual and power constructions tools and instruct new hires on their correct usage
- Perform final inspections at the end of projects and complete detailed reports

CARPENTER

Recreation and Park Commission for the Parish of East Baton Rouge June 2013-March 2015

- Constructed, maintained, and repaired small buildings, including framework, door, and window installation
- Inspected playgrounds for safety, performed repairs, and erected new recreation equipment
- Maintained and repaired historical structures using authentic materials and techniques to respect their unique features